Hello everyone, I'm Molly, I'm here again.
Did you watch our new function live broadcast yesterday?
Welcome, thank you for welcoming me, I watched it, how do you feel, do you think our
Samantha teacher is very sweet and cute?
It looks like everyone is secretly watching it with their headphones, thank you very much for your praise.
The new function is very practical, thank you.
Dongge, Shanghai, I think your ID seems to be very familiar.
I accidentally turned on BDDBD, but there is still a live broadcast today, don't you all know that there is a basic series function live broadcast by Ms. Molly today?
估计很多人下班到家吃饭吧,看莫莉老师的直播难道不下饭吗?
由于很多人不知道我们基础系列直播的素材该在哪里找,所以我们制作了一个图片,我们可以到我们的Close3D微信公众号后台回复链接,这样就可以获得我们每一节课的素材。
我们的直播会不定期有彩蛋掉落,大家如果有想要看的直播的话呢,我们就会在这里彩蛋掉落。
如果有想要看的直播的话呢,可以去我们的微信公众号后台对我们的小衰君进行许愿,小衰君会把你们的愿望整理好给我的哦。
今天我们的后面就会有一个彩蛋的系列,不知道大家期不期待呢?
如果有想要看的直播的话呢,我们就会在这里彩蛋掉落。
什么彩蛋?一看这位同学就没有仔细的关注我们的微信公众号。
我们每一次的课程会提前在公众号发出来喔。
然后我们今天呢主要是要吃这么一条裤子呢。
然后现在呢,我们来就是开始做了.
然后今天呢是要吃这么一条裤子呢。
First, open a virtual model in the library window.
Open the DxF file in the library.
Now the DxF file is in the 2D window.
Now we are going to do the work that we always talk about.
This is the work that we always talk about.
We are going to make them symmetrical.
Here we use the adjustment panel tool to select the back panel.
Just select all the back panels.
On the back panel, right click and click.
There is a symmetrical panel and a line below the column link panel.
The shortcut is Ctrl plus D.
Press it, choose it, and then we can press Shift.
Put it horizontally to the other side.
Next, we reset the 2D position in the 3D window.
Then open the model's arrangement point.
Now we select all the panels in the frame.
Move it away.
Click on the blank to cancel the selection.
We can see that there is a pocket panel and a front panel.
There should be a layer relationship between them.
Now we are going to select this pocket panel.
Use the adjustment panel tool to place the pocket panel below the front panel.
Let's place it below the front panel.
We can rotate the view to see a layer relationship between them.
After placing it, we come back to the 2D window.
Select the pants panel, front panel, and pocket panel.
We can select Ctrl plus D.
Press it, choose it, and then we can press Shift.
Put it horizontally to the other side.
We can see that in the 3D window, the other side is copied in the same way.
This makes it easier for us to work.
We don't need to place the pockets at the same time.
We don't need to place the pockets twice.
We can see that in the 2D window,
we can see that there is a layer relationship between the front and back panels.
We need to place the right front panel on the top of the left front panel.
We can also use the adjustment panel tool to arrange it.
Press Ctrl plus D.
Now let's copy the pants panel.
Right-click on the pants panel and select Copy.
Right-click on the blank area and select Paste.
Put down the pants panel.
Here we don't need to use the adjustment panel tool.
Now let's see the
readout panel.
We can see that all the layers are now in this,
and we can detect the relationship between the two panels.
You can now see that there is a layer relationship between them.
We can see that there is a layer in this panel.
Right-click on the pants panel,
and let's put down the pants panel.
Press Ctrl plus D.
After arranging all the layers,
we now arrange the panels on the virtual model.
We choose the pants panel,
the front pants of the pants,
and then press Shift,
choose the pocket panel,
and then put them together on the model arrangement point.
Then you can pull the attribute editor to the bottom,
and use the purple menu in the arrangement.
We can make some adjustments to it.
Then select the left and right belts at the same time,
and then arrange them together.
We can see that when arranging,
there is a layer relationship between them.
Now we press the 8 on the keyboard,
you can see that
we can turn the view to the back view.
We can select the pants panel at the same time,
and then arrange it to the arrangement point.
Also use the purple panel in the arrangement in the attribute editor,
you can make some adjustments to it.
Arrange the belt at the back.
Now let's arrange these two panels.
We can select these two panels at the same time,
put it on the arrangement point in the front,
and then press them together,
use the positional ball to move them.
We put it in the front pocket of the right panel.
Then press the 8 on the keyboard,
and then the opposite side,
put it on the wrong point.
All right,
let's see what we have.
It's different from what I see,
clean up glass.
Use the wet tissue that I used earlier,
then darken the area a little bit,
we can now see that we have the two surrounded panels.
You can see the buying order on the left,
Too hot.
Let's first sew the pocket panel and the front pocket panel together.
We will use the free sewing tool to sew the overlap position.
After sewing, use the edge sewing tool to frame the two sets of sewing lines.
In the edge sewing tool, we need to change the sewing line type to toned.
After this simulation, this panel will be more even.
Now we can use the free sewing tool to sew the two pants together.
When sewing, we need to...
Especially when the inner line is sewn together, we need to be careful that the inner side of the front left is the inner side of the front left and the inner side of the back right is the inner side of the front right.
Don't sew it wrong or sew it into a skirt.
We can check the sewing line in 3D window.
Now let's sew the rest of the parts together.
In the same way, we only sew the lower half of the front door.
The upper half of the front door needs to be sewed with the front door.
Now let's sew the side of the pocket.
Here we need to use the M-N sewing line tool.
We put the mouse in the free sewing tool.
On the sewing line tool, left-click and long-click.
In the tool bar, select M-N free sewing.
Then select the M-N sewing line.
Then press the car back.
Then press the car back again.
Now let's sew the waistband to the waistband.
Here we are on the M-N free sewing line.
Left-click and long-click again.
This is the area that we want to sew the waistband on.
The waistband is now sewn in the right place.
Make sure the waistband is sewn in the right place.
Now we will sew the pocket and the front pocket.
For sewing, press SHIFT and sew.
Be careful of the sewing line.
The front pocket needs to be sewn in the right direction.
Press SHIFT to close the pocket.
Then press SHIFT and close the pocket.
Then sew the back of the waist belt and the side of the waist belt
Next, we are going to make the buttonhole of this pair of pants
We first sew the buttonhole on the right side of the right side of the right side of the buttonhole with a sewing machine
Here we need to change the sewing line type to TUN
Then sew the top of the buttonhole to the top of the pants
Here we also need to change the sewing line type
Then we use the hook and loop tool to cross the button as I
Hook the front door of the front buttonhole as the inner line
We can press the return car
This way it becomes the inner line
We can use the free sewing line tool to sew it together with the buttonhole
Then we need to sew the buttonhole on the left side with the buttonhole on the left
We sew the top with the waist belt
Here we don't need to change its sewing line type
Now we use the buttonhole tool
First we use the buttonhole tool
We need to select the two parts of these two part
The longest straight line
Then press the button on the straight line of the part
Choose the inner line part
Then we enter a value of 13 mm here in the point
Press the return car
Then use the line sewing tool to sew it together
Then use the machine to sew the center of the skirt
Now we are going to make a button for the waist.
We choose the button tool.
On the left front waist, click on the left button.
You can put down a button.
Then in the 3D tool bar, click on the left button on the button tool.
A button will appear.
We choose the button tool.
On the right front pocket panel, click on the left button.
You create a button.
Then select the move button.
On the button tool, click on the left button.
We can modify its angle in the attribute editor.
Let it be parallel to this basic line.
After that, we can use the fine button tool.
Click on the button.
Click on the button button.
Then click on the button button.
Close this button for it.
Now we are going to select the move button tool.
On the button tool bar, click on the left button.
We can see that there is a conflict at the bottom of the attribute editor.
We need to click on the button button to close the conflict.
This will make the simulation more stable.
Now we click on the Shift button to select all the belt panels.
We select the belt panels in the attribute editor.
Click on the button button.
Then drag the edit button to the bottom.
We open the triangle.
We click on the option box.
We select the belt panels.
We can see that we have added a lot of preset.
If you listen carefully to the five points yesterday,
and the new function is introduced,
you will find that there is a function explanation.
I will not explain it in detail.
We select the appropriate one.
After selecting, we can rotate to see if all the belt panels have been sewn correctly.
After sewing, we open the simulation.
We can see that the belt panel has been successfully made.
Now we select the move button tool.
If we click on the left button on the right, we will find that there is a C position.
What is this?
When we can change the C position, we can see that the button is moving in the 3D window.
Similarly, we can see that there is a green dot in the 2D window.
It is also moving.
We now adjust it to 0 and press simulate.
You can observe the changes in the 3D window.
Now we pull it to the maximum, pull it to 100, and then press simulate again.
You can see that this is different from the 0 just now.
You can also adjust the position of this C to meet the needs of the button C position.
After making it, we will now change the model position to a vertical position.
Now we can see that on the left front and right front panels, there seems to be an internal line.
But in fact, we only need the internal line on the right front panel.
Then we can see that on the front panel panel,
right-click on the right-hand panel,
select the bottom right-hand panel, and choose to remove the joint.
In this way, we can remove the joint of the two front panels,
and click to select the internal line of the left front panel and delete it.
In this way, the internal line is gone.
Next, we are going to enter today's menu section.
So, do you have any questions about this pair of pants?
Xiaoxi likes Xiaoxi best at night.
Do you only like Xiaoxi, don't you like Jasmine?
The durian is 19.8 yuan per catty.
Is it cheap?
Not bad.
Next is our menu section.
Next, we are going to enter our menu section.
Our menu today is...
We have...
Dress.
And then...
We also have our...
Under the mode here, there is a flower arrangement mode.
And then we will teach you how to make a self-designed name line.
And then there is another one.
It is...
A function of Xiaoxi Jun's wish.
Xiaoxi Jun told me about it.
Finally, what we are going to talk about is how we are going to do the show.
The pattern is pasted in the same direction?
Yes, it is in the same direction.
We can hide the pants like this.
We can see that these three are pants in the same direction.
But the point is we are going to make one button.
There's a button in the front, this button is in the back.
The button is on the front.
And then...
We have to place it here.
We are going to put it on the front of our dress.
Now we are going to...
Not...
Don't put on...
Is the necklace on?
Oh, the necklace is inside.
So we usually don't put it on.
If you want to put it on, you can make a small pattern and put it in it.
Can you take a look at the draw?
This is arranged in our later course
You can look forward to it
Now let's open a T-shirt
This T-shirt is in our library
This simple T-shirt in Garment
Let's open this T-shirt
No need to save
In this dialogue box
We need to choose Add
If you choose to open it
The pants will be gone
So we choose Add
Click OK
But we need it inside the pants, and when we open the model, we can see that this T-shirt panel will appear on the outside of the pants panel.
So how do we put it inside? We can select the T-shirt panel, and then we can see a layer in the property editor to simulate the property of the purple menu.
We can set a layer here as "-1", and click OK when the menu is selected.
Now let's open the simulation again.
Now we can see that the T-shirt clothes are already inside the pants panel.
After the simulation is stable, we will reset the layer to "-0", and then open the simulation again.
Our system will automatically record its layer settings. You can rest assured about this.
In addition to adjusting the layer of the T-shirt panel, we can also adjust the layer of the pants panel.
We can now press Ctrl-Z to undo it, and go back to the initial state.
We can also select all the pants panels, and set the layer here to "-1".
We can also set the layer here to "-1", and click OK when the menu is selected.
We can open the simulation again.
We can see that the T-shirt panel is still in the pants panel.
After the simulation is stable, we will reset the layer of the pants panel to "-0".
In this way, the pants panel is ready to wear.
If the top and bottom of the T-shirt are not as narrow as this one,
or if the top and bottom are very large,
we can use the end-shape shrink or the golden-shape shrink to adjust the size of the pattern on the OBJ.
How to adjust the size of the pattern on the OBJ?
We can adjust the size of the pattern on the OBJ.
We can't adjust the size of the pattern on the OBJ right now.
We can't adjust the size of the pattern on the OBJ.
Now, let's draw a fabric for the pants and top.
In the Fabric fabric,
draw a fabric for the pants.
The fabric is suitable for making a suit case.
Then, for the top, we give it a needle fabric.
We can press it and put it directly into the fabric window panel.
We will copy this fabric.
Then, we open the simulation and give an application.
We will apply the physical properties of this pattern to the top of the suit.
Then, we close the simulation again.
We can adjust the color to it.
If you don't know which fabric is the T-shirt or the pants,
we can click on the left button on any pattern of the T-shirt or pants.
We can click on the left button on any pattern of the T-shirt or pants.
and then, we won't have to scale the size.
Then, when you open the simulation,
look at the almost 1% of the material in the tav.
We apply the extra value from the drag scale.
We enable the next tag- regen.
Then, come back to the human.
When we exit the human,
We can give it a color
This is a dark gray
Then click OK
Then to modify its
Lock and lock eyes
We can choose the lock in the room window
Click to lock eyes
We can choose this shape at the bottom
In the shape tool, choose a suitable or your favorite type of button
You can also choose to customize the button
If you have listened to Ms. Molly's last lesson, you should know
How to explain our customized button
How to make
We can pull the attribute editor to the bottom
There is a type here in the attribute
We can change it here
Change to a metal type
You can also change it to a color
Give it grey
You can also choose the button at the door
And click on this button
In the attribute editor
You can also change its shape to it
You can also change the color of the t-shirt.
Now let's give this t-shirt a texture.
We can choose a four-dimensional texture.
We can click on the material in the object window and drag it to the texture box.
Let's see where the playback is.
We have our playback on BDBD.
Now we can see that
this texture is applied to this t-shirt.
We can use the texture to edit the texture here.
We can also edit the texture in the second window.
If we want to position it here,
or position it,
we can do it here.
It's more complicated here.
Then we can click on our mode.
Click on our mode,
and then enter our hard flower playback mode at the bottom of the mode.
Here we can see this t-shirt.
In the second window,
we can see something like a cloth.
We can set the width of this fabric in the attribute editor.
Here we can choose these fabric widths,
and we can also input them ourselves at the bottom.
Here we choose a 58-inch width.
Click on the
In the second window,
we can moved about one figure on the unit alone.
We can see its location movement in the 3D window.
Now we need to restore these two versions to a new one.
We can click on this version on this version.
This is a stolen version.
And then on the top of this little button here, press it to rotate it.
We need to press Shift here.
When we rotate it, we can feel that there is a curtain.
This is a 45 degree rotation or a 90 degree指示.
Let's rotate it 180 degrees.
Then put the two of them side by side.
So we can see that the two of them are restored.
You can also choose these two.
Right-click to align to the middle.
That's it.
We can move it.
Here's the curtain version.
We can select the frame for it.
Put it next to it.
Then we right-click on it.
And then we can align it to it.
And then we put it on the right-hand side.
Then we arrange these two sleeves for it.
After arranging, we can see on the left side of the page that there is a 0.629.8 mm.
This is the material needed to make a T-shirt like this.
We can click on the fabric of the pants in the object window.
In this way, we can adjust the position of the flower arrangement of the pants in the 2D window.
We can also see the material needed here.
In addition to being in the object window,
there are also two pieces of fabric on the top of the 2D window.
We can also click on them at the same time,
and then choose the fabric we need.
When to make a sweater?
If we make a sweater in the later stage,
we will have a special live broadcast in the later stage.
You can look forward to it.
The fabric does not have a seam.
This is not accurate.
We can go back to the simulation mode.
We have a sewing tool in the 2D tool.
We can add a pattern to the fabric.
We can set the depth of the sole here,
including the spicy vermicelli or other type,
which allows us to chili the том's pattern.
In the shell plating zone,
You can see the pattern here and see it.
Press the Y button,
to adjust the dense Press the Y button,
Inasmuch as the densityShow 38 as shown.
As the density is D,
Now let's go back to the simulation mode
Then change our tool to 3D tool and change it to move
Now let's make a self-defined name line
Is there anyone interested in this feature?
Thank you for your support
We can choose a name line at the object window
Then we can click this name line at the object window
Then choose this name line
First of all, let's
Let's first change the object type to Textual type
Then at the bottom we can see that there is a text
We can put a text here that has already been created
Also, we can change the text type to text type
Then we can change the text type to text type
You can drag it directly to this text
Next, let's use the name line tool
We can long press on the name line tool
There are modern name lines, free name lines
And forensic name line tools
We choose the appropriate name line tool
we can add it to the threshold of the T-shape.
Now we can see that we have added a self-defined line like this.
We can also adjust the diameter of the self-defined line.
We can also adjust the number of its lines.
We can also adjust the length of the line.
We can also adjust the thickness of the line.
We can also change its type and color.
We can also use the color tool to identify its color.
This is how we define our own line.
I'm afraid I missed something in the bathroom.
You can watch our live broadcast if you missed something.
Can I add different lines?
Yes, you can.
so you can add more to it, and modify its species
you can also make it a self-designed one
you can set it up face to face, that's fine
here we will
we can change a place to give it
increase its sleeve
so that you can see it more clearly
we choose this name line
and then at the bottom
under the attribute editor
there is an environment setting
grid surface
we can set the grid surface to all
like this, its front
its
inside the sleeve
and the surface of the sleeve panel
are all like this
such a name line
I hope you can hear me well
thank you
thank you, Yana
love to drink coconut milk
how to make a name line pattern
you can scan the name line pattern
and you can also make it with PS
just click the name bar
there is another question
what if we set the name line
Oh, our little C-Jun has already answered this one.
After we've finished making this one,
we'll move on to today's biggest challenge,
which is also a feature that everyone is looking forward to.
We'll make a walkthrough.
How can we make a walkthrough?
I see a lot of people are looking forward to a walkthrough.
We can choose the animation mode under the mode.
Here, our simulation type will be called animation mode.
We'll change it to animation completion.
We'll also set up a double-click in the Library Avatar file.
We can go into the Motion folder,
and open it with the double-click.
We'll choose one of its walkthroughs,
and then click OK.
That's it.
We'll check if this is the 5.2 version.
Is this the 5.2 version?
Yes, I'm using the 5.2 version.
However, I forgot to click the download button.
When the download button shows a big N sign,
you'll definitely need to click it to download it.
From here, you'll see that there's a...
Here we are in a walkthrough page.
After selecting the walkthrough scene,
we can click here to record.
This way we can start the walkthrough.
Now you can see that this is a model in the walkthrough.
You can create your own buttons.
btn is our button file.
It can be customized to create buttons.
In our last live broadcast,
we talked about how to customize buttons.
If you don't know how to customize your own buttons,
you can check out our last live broadcast.
If you have time later,
I can explain again.
Let's start the walkthrough.
If you have time later,
I can explain again.
Let's start the walkthrough.
If you have time later,
I can explain again.
Let's start the walkthrough.
For the first time,
We can't do a lot of running shows with him yet.
Good running show, good running show.
Thank you, Durian Bai Jia.
5.2 has real-time rendering, awesome.
Yes, we can do real-time rendering.
We can open the high-quality rendering of the 3D window like this.
This is a state of real-time rendering.
After the running show is finished,
our recording will automatically stop.
We can drag the progress bar to the front.
Then there is a wave here,
click the button to open it.
Now we can see a model running show like this.
Then we can drag the blue progress bar above it
to select its running show range.
If we drag the blue progress bar above it,
then there is only this blue bar
which is only available for running shows.
Only this blue bar can run running shows in a selected area.
After the running shows are finished,
let's go back to the situational mode once again.
Let's go back to the situational mode once again.
Someone just asked how to edit the scene
If you want to edit the scene, you need to open the stage in the library window
This stage needs to be added before recording
Since I have finished recording the walkthrough, I won't be showing this one
After the walkthrough, we can click on the rendering
Then enter the rendering mode here
We can click on the picture
In the attribute editor, there is a picture or video
Click on it and choose animation
Then select the area we just selected
Then click on the save video
Then choose the size of the picture, we can choose A4
Then we can start rendering the animation
Since this rendering takes a lot of time
I have already made a small video
Let me show you
This is our work for rendering the walkthrough
Which is what we want
And here, we have the music
If you want the music as well
If you want to add music, you can add the music you want in the video editing software.
The model's face can be put on makeup in the PS.
Can I change other actions? Yes, you can.
But because I didn't click on the download button,
so now there's only one action.
If you click on the download button,
you can choose several actions.
Now we return the model to its original state.
You can see the model is now in the original state.
You can see the model has been changed.
The model is now in the original state.
Finally, let's make a quality adjustment.
Before that,
since the waist of our pants is usually double-layered,
we will choose all the pants waist plates
and increase the thickness of the hemline.
Before that,
you will choose all the pants the hemline of the pants.
Then, under the material element,
there will be a thickness,
is 0.38 mm.
When we increase the hemline thickness,
we also give it a thickness of 0.3 mm.
Then here,
we open the double-layer performance.
In this way, we can see that this waist is a double-layer version.
After we're done, we're going to give it a higher physical quality.
Then click OK.
Then click simulate.
After opening the simulation, our pants are done.
Do you have any questions about today's live stream?
Next, let's move on to today's Q&A session.
If you have any questions, please leave them in the comments.
If you don't have any questions, please ask them in the comments.
The materials we use for each live stream can be found at the back of our WeChat official account.
Just reply to the link and you can get our live stream materials.
Next, how to make a folding effect?
Did you ask this question in the 5.2 live stream yesterday?
Our professor Samantha answered this question yesterday.
Please look at the chat box.
Let's take a look at XiaoCuiJun's answer.
What tools do you have more than 5.2 and 5.1.330?
You didn't listen carefully to our 5.2 new function live broadcast yesterday.
So, that makes Smith angry.
How to improve the authenticity of the rendering?
First, you need to scan the texture and create the texture of the light and shadow.
including lighting
I want to hear how to use light
We will have a live stream on this topic in the later part of the video
Please look forward to it
The live stream of our 5.2 new feature has been released
If you have any questions about the new feature
You can go to the live stream of the new feature
I heard that 5.2 is very good
Yes, our 5.2 is very good
Thank you
Thank you, thank you
What are the principles and functions of the line-of-sight sticker?
I can't remember
I'm sorry, I'll drink some water
Let me record a demo for you guys
Let's take this pair of pants.
We can see that the strength is set to 0.
We can see that it doesn't have such a rough texture.
And when we set the strength to 100, we can see that the roughness is very, very obvious.
Hair clippings can increase the authenticity of your fabric.
And then it shows the roughness of your fabric.
In our process of manufacturing the fabric,
We can upload this file to the Klossette supply list.
And then we can also have a material list in 5.2 mode.
We can see the cost of the material in the material list.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask us in the Q&A section of the Q&A section.
You can follow our WeChat official account.
This way, you can get our live broadcasts and live broadcasts at any time.
You can see the previous broadcasts on Bilibili.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask.
You can follow our WeChat official account.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask us in the Q&A section of the Q&A section.
Thank you all for watching this video.
Please feel free to add comments.
we can choose our
a button
we can adjust the thickness here
ah, the mushroom you want, is it this button?
you can adjust the thickness here
ok
next, I will do it like this
you can see that the thickness is the size of this mushroom
so you can adjust the thickness if you like
and you can adjust the thickness too
Why does the rendering resolution of 300 and 800 look the same?
How big is the image size of your rendering?
We can choose its image size here.
We generally recommend the image size of A4.
What mushroom just now?
The one in the text, we can directly give it the text in the text.
Do you have any questions?
How to use the material?
I'm a beginner.
You can get our live material by replying to the link in the background of our WeChat official account.
And you can download the material on our Baidu cloud.
Tilted text.
If you have any questions, you can also go to our official website to ask questions.
There will be users from all over the world answering your questions.
Do you have any lessons for beginners?
Now this is a beginner's lesson.
This is our basic series of live broadcasts.
How to close the website?
Oh, you can go directly to our software page.
There is a handbook on the top of the main menu bar.
Here, here you can...
There is online teaching, which is one of our learning videos.
Then long-term questions, answers, community.
These can be directly clicked.
They can be directly linked to our official website.
Our official website is the website address is 3w.clou3d.com.
3w.clou3d.com.
Alright when studying Chinese with a hard drive.
Is there any more questions?
If no questions, then our live broadcast ends here.
nee is also a worry.
I can't make it with așinai drawing with aśinai drawing.
You can set the type that is Citin as plastic.
Such words, you can try.
If you don't have any questions, this is the end of our live broadcast.
You can follow our WeChat account and get our live broadcast materials by replying to the link in the background.
You can also post your excellent works on Weibo and WeChat and show them to us.
You can also follow our official Douyin live broadcast account.
This is the end of our live broadcast.
See you next time. Bye bye.
Our live broadcast is every Friday at 8pm.
Once every two weeks.
I hope you can follow us.
Bye bye.
Happy May 1st.
See you next time.